<PAMDataset>
  <Metadata>
    <MDI key="lat#long_name">latitude</MDI>
    <MDI key="lat#standard_name">latitude</MDI>
    <MDI key="lat#units">degrees_north</MDI>
    <MDI key="lon#long_name">longitude</MDI>
    <MDI key="lon#standard_name">longitude</MDI>
    <MDI key="lon#units">degrees_east</MDI>
    <MDI key="NC_GLOBAL#comment">dataType IDentifier definitions\n0 - Land\n10 Singlebeam - depth value collected by a single beam echo-sounder\n11 Multibeam - depth value collected by a multibeam echo-sounder\n12 Seismic - depth value colleced by seismic methods\n13 Isolated sounding - depth value that is not part of a regular survey or trackline\n14 ENC sounding - depth value extracted from an Electronic Navigation Chart (ENC)\n15 Lidar - depth derived from a bathymetric lidar sensor\n16 Optical - Depth measured by optical light sensor\n17 Combination of direct measurement methods\nIn-direct Methods\n40 Predicted based on satellite-derived gravity data - depth value is an interpolated value guided by satellite-derived gravity data\n41 Interpolated based on a computer algorithm - depth value is an interpolated value based on a computer algorithm (e.g. Generic Mapping Tools)\n42 Digital bathymetric contours from charts - depth value taken from a bathymetric contour data set\n43 Digital bathymetric contours from ENCs - depth value taken from bathymetric contours from an Electronic Navigation Chart (ENC)\n44 Bathymetric sounding - depth value at this location is constrained by bathymetric sounding(s) within a gridded data set where interpolation between sounding points is guided by satellite-derived gravity data\n45 Predicted based on airborne (helicopter/flight)-derived gravity data\nUnknown\n70 Pre-generated grid - depth value is taken from a pre-generated grid that is based on mixed source data types, e.g. single beam, multibeam, interpolation etc.\n71 Unknown source - depth value from an unknown source\n72 Steering points - depth value used to constrain the grid in areas of poor data coverage\n</MDI>
    <MDI key="NC_GLOBAL#Conventions">CF-1.5</MDI>
    <MDI key="NC_GLOBAL#GDAL">GDAL 3.0.1, released 2019/06/28</MDI>
    <MDI key="NC_GLOBAL#history">Mon Aug 10 15:46:31 2020: GDAL CreateCopy( GEBCO_2020_TID_cf.nc, ... )
Information on the development of the data set and the source data sets included in the grid can be found in the data set documentation available from https://www.gebco.net</MDI>
    <MDI key="NC_GLOBAL#institution">On behalf of the General Bathymetric Chart of the Oceans (GEBCO), the data are held at the British Oceanographic Data Centre (BODC).</MDI>
    <MDI key="NC_GLOBAL#node_offset">1</MDI>
    <MDI key="NC_GLOBAL#references">DOI: 10.5285/836f016a-33be-6ddc-e053-6c86abc0788e</MDI>
    <MDI key="NC_GLOBAL#source">The GEBCO_2020 Grid is the latest global bathymetric product released by the General Bathymetric Chart of the Oceans (GEBCO) and has been developed through the Nippon Foundation-GEBCO Seabed 2030 Project. This is a collaborative project between the Nippon Foundation of Japan and GEBCO. The Seabed 2030 Project aims to bring together all available bathymetric data to produce the definitive map of the world ocean floor and make it available to all.</MDI>
    <MDI key="NC_GLOBAL#title">The GEBCO_2020 Grid Type Identifier</MDI>
    <MDI key="tid#flag_meanings">Land Singlebeam Multibeam Seismic Isolated_sounding ENC_sounding Lidar Optical Combined predicted_altimetry interpolated contour_charts contour_ENC bathymetric_sounding predicted_airborne pre-generated_grid unknown steering_point</MDI>
    <MDI key="tid#flag_values">{0,10,11,12,13,14,15,16,17,40,41,42,43,44,45,70,71,72}</MDI>
    <MDI key="tid#long_name">GEBCO Type Identifier</MDI>
    <MDI key="tid#sdn_parameter_name">Source identifer of GEBCO grid cell data</MDI>
    <MDI key="tid#sdn_parameter_urn">SDN:P01::GEBCOSRC</MDI>
    <MDI key="tid#sdn_uom_name">Dimensionless</MDI>
    <MDI key="tid#sdn_uom_urn">SDN:P06:UUUU</MDI>
    <MDI key="tid#units">1</MDI>
    <MDI key="tid#valid_range">{-128,127}</MDI>
    <MDI key="tid#_FillValue">127</MDI>
    <MDI key="tid#_Unsigned">false</MDI>
  </Metadata>
  <PAMRasterBand band="1">
    <UnitType>1</UnitType>
    <Metadata>
      <MDI key="flag_meanings">Land Singlebeam Multibeam Seismic Isolated_sounding ENC_sounding Lidar Optical Combined predicted_altimetry interpolated contour_charts contour_ENC bathymetric_sounding predicted_airborne pre-generated_grid unknown steering_point</MDI>
      <MDI key="flag_values">{0,10,11,12,13,14,15,16,17,40,41,42,43,44,45,70,71,72}</MDI>
      <MDI key="long_name">GEBCO Type Identifier</MDI>
      <MDI key="NETCDF_VARNAME">tid</MDI>
      <MDI key="sdn_parameter_name">Source identifer of GEBCO grid cell data</MDI>
      <MDI key="sdn_parameter_urn">SDN:P01::GEBCOSRC</MDI>
      <MDI key="sdn_uom_name">Dimensionless</MDI>
      <MDI key="sdn_uom_urn">SDN:P06:UUUU</MDI>
      <MDI key="units">1</MDI>
      <MDI key="valid_range">{-128,127}</MDI>
      <MDI key="_FillValue">127</MDI>
      <MDI key="_Unsigned">false</MDI>
    </Metadata>
  </PAMRasterBand>
</PAMDataset>
